Guide to the Andrei Voznesenskii Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2: Correspondence
  - Subseries 2.3: Collected Notes Sent to A.Voznesenskii During Poetry Readings
    - Collected notes sent to A.A.Voznesenskii during poetry readings [2 of 6]n.d., Handwritten notes, mostly anonymous, 12 pages of different size, mostly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 36)
      Boris Pasternak; Vladimir Vysotskii; Rodion Shchedrin; Maiia Plisetskaia; Rabindranath Tagore.
    - Collected notes sent to A.A.Voznesenskii during poetry readings [3 of 6]01.21.1996; n.d., Handwritten notes, mostly anonymous, 12 pages of different size, mostly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 37)
      Collected notes (one of them from Z.Boguslavskaia ?).
      Nikolai Gogol'; Aleksei Kruchenykh; B.V.Vasiliev; Grigorii Iavlinskii; Vladimir Lenin; Valeriia Novodvorskaia; Iurii Afanasiev; Evgenii Evtushenko [Yevtushenko]; Vladimir Vysotskii.
    - Collected notes sent to A.A.Voznesenskii during poetry readings [4 of 6]n.d., Handwritten notes, mostly anonymous, 12 pages of different size, mostly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 38)
      Iu.A.Dvoriashin; Evgenii Evtushenko [Yevtushenko]; Andrei [?] Tarkovskii.
    - Collected notes sent to A.A.Voznesenskii during poetry readings [5 of 6]n.d., Handwritten notes, mostly anonymous, 23 pages of different size and one postcard, mostly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 39)
      Boris Pasternak; Marilyn Monroe; Vladimir Vysotskii; Michelangelo Buonarroti; Viktoriia [?] Pavlova.
    - Collected notes sent to A.A.Voznesenskii during poetry readings [6 of 6]n.d., Handwritten notes, mostly anonymous, 19 pages of different size, mostly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 40)
      Vladimir Lenin; Michelangelo Buonarroti; Evgeniia Ul'chenko; Leonid Zhukhovitskii; Sergei Dovlatov; Nikolai [?] Rerikh.
  - Subseries 2.4: Other Correspondence
    - Azov, P.& E., A letter to "Literaturnaia gazeta"n.d. [after 03.10.1984], A handwritten letter, 2 pages, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 41)
      A letter (forwarded to A.Voznesenskii by the staff of "Literaturnaia gazeta" ?).
      Igor' Severianin; Vera Korendi; Pavel Azov; Elena [?] Azova.; "Literaturnaia gazeta".
    - Blanchemaison, C., An invitation letter to Bella Akhmadoulina10.17.2001, A typewritten invitation card with handwritten additions / corrections, an unposted envelope, and a typewritten note on a piece of paper originally attached to the card. Slightly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 42)
      An invitation (with an envelope) to Bella Akhmadoulina from the French Ambassador in Russia.
      Bella Akhmadoulina; Claude Blanchemaison.
    - Bobovich, G.A., A letter to the magazine "Ogonek"03.31.1992, A typewritten letter with handwritten additions / corrections, 1 page, and a posted envelope, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 43)
      A letter (forwarded to A.Voznesenskii by the staff of "Ogonek" ?). Incl. also an envelope.
      Aleksandr Kerenskii; Tatiana Iakovleva; Osip Brik; Vladimir Maiakovskii; Lilia Brik; Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis; Galina Vishnevskaia; Andrei Voznesenskii.; "Ogonek".
    - Bogdanova, Iu., A letter to Konstantin Kedrov12.25.2000, A typewritten letter, 1 page, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 44)
      Konstantin Kedrov; Salvador Dali; Andrei Voznesenskii; Ekaterina Lishankova; Iuliia Bogdanova.
    - Braman [Bramen], L., A letter to Prof. Ugriumov11.04.1978, A typewritten letter in English with a typewritten Russian translation (with a handwritten signature), 2 pages, and an unposted envelope with a handwritten note on it. Damaged. (Box 22, Folder 45)
      A letter in English with its Russian translation and an envelope with a handwritten note on it from Z.Boguslavskaia [?] to A.Voznesenskii concerning L.Braman's case.
      Professor Ugriumov [Ugrjumov]; Zoia Boguslavskaia; Andrei Voznesenskii; Lawrence Braman.; Central Neurosurgical Institute u.m. [?] Polenov [Tsentral'nyi neirokhirurgicheskii institut imeni Polenova]; The Institute of Rehabilitation Medicine in New York City.
    - Chugunnikov, S., A letter to the magazine "Russkaia Amerika"04.21.1992, A handwritten letter, 1 page, a typescript of a poem, 10 pages (with a handwritten note on the other side of the last page), and a posted envelope, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 46)
      A letter, a typescript of a poem by S.Chugunnikov with a handwritten note on the other side of the last page, and an envelope.
      Serzh [Sergei] Chugunnikov.; "Russkaia Amerika".
    - Dinaburgskii, V.D., A letter [?] to the editors of the newspaper "Sovietskaia kul'tura"10.16.1986 [?], An empty posted envelope, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 47)
      An envelope.
      V.D.Dinaburgskii.; "Sovietskaia kul'tura".
    - For R.Khamdanovn.d., An empty posted envelope with numerous handwritten notes, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 48)
      An envelope with the names of Iurii Bashmet (printed) and Zoia Boguslavskaia (handwritten) and with other handwritten notes.
      Iurii Bashmet; Zoia Boguslavskaia; R.Khamdanov.
    - Lobyrev, A.A., A letter to Iu.M.Luzhkovn.d., A typewritten letter and a typewritten list of members of the condomimium "The Writer's House" with handwritten notes / corrections on the both sides of the list, 2 pages total, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 49)
      A letter to the major of Moscow and a list of members of the condomimium "The Writer's House" ("Dom pisatelia") with notes / corrections on the both sides of the list.
      Iurii Luzhkov; Bulat Okudzhava; Mikhail Zhvanetskii; Andrei Voznesenskii; Vladimir Makanin; Iurii Davydov; Viacheslav Pietsukh; Georgii Vladimov; Aleksandr Ginsburg; Galina Guseva; Ruslan Dzhopua; Viktor Erofeev; Anatolii Kim; Vadim Kozulin; Aleksandr Lobyrev; Iunna Morits; Iuz Aleshkovskii; Evgenii Rein; Teimuraz Svanidze; Oleg Stashkevich; Lev Timofeev; Aleksandr Tkachenko; Oleg Chukhontsev; Larisa Shul'man.; "The Writer's House" ("Dom pisatelia").
    - Mekhedova, L., A letter to Alla Borisovna [Pougacheva ?]06.17.1993, A typewritten letter, 1 page, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 50)
      Larisa Mekhedova; Alla Pougacheva [?].
    - Mel'nikov, [?], A letter to General-Major Pastushikhin09.06.1943, A photocopy of an official typewritten letter with a handwritten signature and numerous handwritten notes, 1 page. (Box 22, Folder 51)
      A photocopy of an official letter from the Chairman of the Executive Committee of Smolensk Regional Committee of Deputies (Ispolnitel'nyi Komitet Smolenskogo Oblastnogo Soveta Deputatov Trudiashchikhsia) Comrade Mel'nikov to General-Major Pastushikhin concerning his inquiry for help to the family of Leutenant Vasilenko.
      General-Major Pastushikhin; Leutenant N.N.Vasilenko.; Executive Committee of Smolensk Regional Committee of Deputies (Ispolnitel'nyi Komitet Smolenskogo Oblastnogo Soveta Deputatov Trudiashchikhsia).
    - Postcardsn.d., Nine unposted postcards, one of them with numerous illegible handwritten notes on the other side, another one with a short handwritten note on the other side, some are slightly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 52)
      Nine unposted postcards, one of them with numerous illegible notes on the other side made by A.Voznesenskii, another one with a short note on the other side.
    - Sample, M.M., Giles, M., & Henry M., A letter to B.N.Polevoi12.15.1978, A typewritten letter with handwritten signatures and a handwritten postscriptum, 1 page, and an unposted envelope with a handwritten note on it, slightly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 53)
      A letter and an envelope with a note on it.
      Boris Polevoi; Valentina G. Brougher; Meredith M. Sample; Mary Giles; Margaret Henry; Andrei Dementiev.; Georgetown University, Washington, D.C.
    - [Unidentified author], A postcard to the editors of the literary journal "Iunost' "08.20.1986 [?], A postcard with a handwritten note (the author's signature is illegible), damaged. (Box 22, Folder 54)
      A note with the information for A.Voznesenskii mentioning his poem "Rov".
      Andrei Voznesenskii.; "Pravda"; "Iunost' ".
    - Universite; de Paris-Sorbonne, A letter to Mikhael A. Ayvasian12.11-21.2001, An empty posted envelope with several handwritten notes on it, damaged. (Box 22, Folder 55)
      An empty envelope with several handwritten notes in Russian on it, two of them illegible, one saying "Dlia Voznesenskogo" ("For Voznesenskii").
      Mikhael A. Ayvasian; Andrei Voznesenskii.; Universite; de Paris-Sorbonne.
    - Villany [?], H. [?], A letter to N.Bogoslouvskaia [?]10.10.1991, A handwritten letter, 1 page, and a posted envelope with a technical handwritten note on it, slightly damaged. (Box 22, Folder 56)
      A letter in French and an envelope.
      H.Villany [?]; Natasha Bogoslouvskaia [?].
- Series 3: Drawings, Sketches, and Visual Poetry
  - Subseries 3.1: A.Voznesenskii's Drawings, Sketches, and Visual Poetry
    - Internetn.d., Marker and / or pencil on paper; clippings w/marker notes; printed visual poetry, 22 leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 1)
      22 leaves devoted to the theme of Internet.
      Viktor Vasnetsov.
    - Popular commercial brands1966-1999; n.d., Marker and / or pencil on paper; printed visual poetry; collages, sometimes attached to cartoon, 31 leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 2)
      31 leaves devoted to the theme of popular commercial brands.
      "Nescafe"; "Whiskas"; "Kitekat"; "Marlboro".
    - Illustrations to Voznesenskii's poem "Kara Karfagena"n.d., Marker on paper, 5 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm., mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 3)
      Illustrations to Voznesenskii's poem "Kara Karfagena".
    - Illustrations to Voznesenskii's poem "Devochka s pirsingom"1999; n.d., Marker on paper / vellum [?]; collage on paper / vellum [?]; marker on a page from a catalog [?], 11 leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. There are short handwritten notes on some leaves. (Othertype 23, Folder 4)
      Illustrations to Voznesenskii's poem "Devochka s pirsingom", some with short handwritten notes.
    - Millennium and International Women's Day (March, 8th)n.d. [1999-2000 ?], Marker / pen / pencil on paper and vellum; printed visual poetry, 30 leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. There are short handwritten notes on some leaves. (Othertype 23, Folder 5)
      30 leaves devoted to topics of Millennium and International Women's Day (March, 8th), some with short handwritten notes.
    - September 11, 2001n.d. [2001 ?], Marker on paper; applications. One sketch includes also a handwritten draft of a poem [?]. Eighteen leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 6)
      18 leaves devoted to the theme of September 11, 2001.
    - A visual theme [1 of 2]n.d., Marker on paper, 21 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm., mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 7)
      21 leaves united by the visual theme of "glasses-2001-2002".
    - A visual theme [2 of 2]n.d., Marker on paper, with fragments of printed poetry collections and handwritten additions / corrections on the other side of some leaves, 21 leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 8)
    - Crucifixion [1 of 2]2002 [?], Marker on paper, 16 leaves of different size, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 9)
      16 leaves united by the theme of crucifixion. Many sketches include the word [the title ?] "Nenavist' " ["Hatred"].
    - Crucifixion [2 of 2]2002 [?], Marker on paper; printed drawings, 17 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm. total, mostly damaged. There are pencil sketches on the other side of the last leaf. (Othertype 23, Folder 10)
      17 leaves united by the theme of crucifixion. Many sketches include the word [the title ?] "Nenavist' " ["Hatred"].
    - Zemfiran.d., Printed visual poetry / pencil on paper, 14 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm. total. (Othertype 23, Folder 11)
      14 leaves devoted to the topic of Zemfira, Russian pop-rock singer.
      Aleksandr Pushkin; Zemfira Ramazanova.
    - A viola and Iurii Bashmet [1 of 2]2001 [?], Marker / pen on paper; printed visual poetry, 18 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm. total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 12)
      18 leaves devoted to the theme of a viola and Iurii Bashmet, Russian violist.
    - A viola and Iurii Bashmet [2 of 2]2001 [?], Marker / pen on paper; printed visual poetry, 18 leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 13)
    - An abstract visual themen.d., Marker on paper, 18 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm., mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 14)
      18 leaves united by an abstract visual theme.
    - A church [1 of 2]n.d., Marker / pencil on paper, 48 leaves of different size (one with a short handwritten note under the sketch), some are damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 15)
      48 leaves devoted to the theme of a church. There is a short handwritten note under one of the sketches saying "Maket budushchego khrama v Podmoskovie" ["A model of a church to be built near Moscow"].
    - A church [2 of 2]n.d., Marker on paper, 43 leaves ca. 29,7 x 21 cm., some are slightly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 16)
      43 leaves devoted to the theme of a church.
    - An abstract visual themen.d., Marker on paper, 13 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm., mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 17)
      13 leaves united by an abstract visual theme.
    - An abstract visual themen.d., Marker on paper, 12 leaves of different size, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 18)
      12 leaves united by an abstract visual theme.
    - A ballerina2001; n.d., Marker on paper / cartoon, with a handwritten note [draft ?] on one leaf, 23 leaves of different size, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 19)
      23 leaves devoted to the theme of a ballerina.
    - A woman; an abstract visual theme2001; n.d., Marker / pen / pencil on paper / cartoon, 7 leaves of different size, mostly damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 20)
      3 leaves united by the theme of a woman and 4 leaves united by abstract visual theme.
    - Aleksandr Pushkin and "Evgenii Onegin"1998 [?]; n.d., Marker / pen on paper / paper attached to cartoon; printed visual poetry, 10 leaves of different size total, some are damaged. (Othertype 23, Folder 21)
      10 leaves devoted to the theme of a Russian poet Aleksandr Pushkin and his novel in verses "Evgenii Onegin".
      Aleksandr Pushkin.
    - Two themesn.d., Printed visual poetry, 5 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm., slightly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 1)
      2 leaves devoted to the theme of the Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts anniversary and 3 leaves united by the theme "Before a course - after a course".
      Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts.
    - Two visual themesn.d., Marker / pen on paper, 26 leaves ca. 29,7 x 21 cm., some are slightly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 2)
      13 leaves united by the visual theme of a "nose" and 13 leaves united by the visual theme of a "cherry".
    - W.H.Auden & W.A.Mozartn.d., Marker / pen on paper; collage; printed visual poetry, 8 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten notes, mostly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 3)
      4 leaves devoted to the poet W.H.Auden and 4 leaves united by the theme of the composer W.A.Mozart.
      Wystan Hugh Auden; Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart.
    - Two visual themes1995-1998 [?]; n.d., Marker on paper, 10 leaves of different size, some with short handwritten notes, mostly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 4)
      4 leaves united by abstract visual theme and 4 leaves united by the theme of "tattooed prick" [?].
    - "Beregite zaik!"n.d., Marker on paper; printed visual poetry. On the other side of one sketch there is a printed fragment of a poem. Ten leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten notes, mostly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 5)
      10 leaves united by the slogan "Beregite zaik!" ["Preserve slutters!"] with a fragment of a poem by A.Voznesenskii on the other side of one leave.
    - "Shar-pei"2000-2001 [?]; n.d., Marker / pen / pencil [?] on paper; printed visual poetry; one printed page with a reproduction of A.Voznesenskii's drawing, 28 leaves of different size total, some are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 6)
      10 leaves of illustrations to A.Voznesenskii's poem "Shar-pei".
    - Two visual themes1994; n.d., Marker / pen on paper, 20 leaves ca. 29,7 x 21 cm., some with short handwritten notes, some are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 7)
      9 leaves united by an abstract visual theme and 11 leaves devoted to the popular Russian newspaper "Argumenty i fakty".
      "Argumenty i fakty".
    - Two themes1997; n.d., Marker / pen / pencil on paper / paper attached to cartoon / toilet paper, 6 leaves of different size total, some items are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 8)
      4 leaves united by the humorous New Year theme with the slogan "Ty sobral kompromat ?" ["Have you collected the compromising data ?"] and 2 leaves devoted to Olby.
    - Two themesn.d., Marker / pen on paper; printed visual poetry; photocopies of a book's pages with reproduction of Voznesenskii's sketches, 22 leaves ca. 29,7 x 21 cm. total, some items are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 9)
      9 leaves of caricatures on N.S.Khrushchev and 13 leaves devoted to the theme of time.
      Nikita Khrushchev.
    - Two themesn.d., Marker on paper; printed versions of the covers of Voznesenskii's poetic collections, 12 leaves of different size total, some items are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 10)
      4 leaves of sketches for the cover of Voznesenskii's poetic collection "Stradivari sostradan'ia" and 8 leaves of sketches for the cover of Voznesenskii's poetic collection "Treugol'naia grusha".
    - Two themesn.d., Marker / pen / pencil on paper; printed visual poetry, 10 leaves ca. 29,7 x 21 cm. total, some with printed fragments of texts on the other side, some items are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 11)
      3 leaves united by an "animal" theme and 7 leaves devoted to the theme of "Eurasian unity".
    - Miscellaneous themes1993 [?] - 1996; n.d., Marker / pen on paper; printed visual poetry, 11 leaves ca. 42,1 x 29,7 cm. total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 12)
      11 leaves devoted to miscellaneous themes.
    - Miscellaneous themes2001 [?]; n.d., Marker / pen / pencil on paper; printed visual poetry, 49 leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 13)
      49 leaves devoted to miscellaneous themes.
    - Miscellaneous themes1990 [?] - 1999; n.d., Marker / pen / pencil on paper; collages; printed visual poetry, 16 leaves of different size total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 14)
      16 leaves devoted to miscellaneous themes.
    - Miscellaneous items1985 - 1995 [?]; n.d., Marker / pen / pencil on paper / vellum; collages; watercolour; craft materials, 11 items of different size total, mostly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 15)
      One Voznesenskii's autoportrait [?] on the other side of hotel paper, two watercolours, the first letter of Voznesenskii's last name cut out of gold-coloured paper, 2 leaves of craft materials, and 5 leaves devoted to miscellaneous topics.
    - Russian money1998; n.d. / date is illegible, Printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon, 10 leaves of different size total, some items are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 16)
      10 leaves devoted to the theme of Russian money / inflation.
    - Miscellaneous themes1998; n.d., Marker / pen [?] on paper; printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon; a photo reproduction [?], 15 leaves of different size total, some items are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 17)
      2 leaves united by the theme of "Nefertiti / garbage", 4 leaves devoted to David Copperfield, 1 portrait of a man, 6 leaves devoted to the theme of a "tiger", and 2 leaves devoted to the theme of "rave".
      David Copperfield.
    - Printed visual poetryn.d., Printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon, 11 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten notes / additions, some are slightly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 18)
      11 leaves of printed visual poetry, including "krugomety".
    - Visual poetryn.d., Marker / pen on paper; printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon, 16 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten corrections / additions, some are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 19)
      16 leaves of visual poetry, including "krugomety".
      Vladimir Lenin; Viktor Erofeev; Elton John; Vladimir Nabokov; Kazimir Malevich; Katherine the Great; Francois-Andre Danican Philidor [?].
    - Printed visual poetry1998 [?]; n.d., Printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon / on cartoon [?], 22 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten additions, mostly damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 20)
      22 leaves of printed visual poetry, including "krugomety".
      Pablo Picasso; Marc Chagall [Shagall]; Dmitrii Shostakovich; Iraklii Andronikov; Anna Akhmatova; Boris Pasternak; Genrikh Neigauz; Nina Dorliak; Oleg [?] Efremov; Sviatoslav Rikhter; Iurii Bashmet; Iulii Gutman; Mstislav Rostropovich; Iurii [Yuri] Temirkanov; Albert Camus.
    - Miscellaneous themes1995 - 1999; n.d., Marker / pen / pencil on paper; printed visual poetry; printed visual poetry attached to paper, 36 items of different size total, some are damaged. (Othertype 24, Folder 21)
      9 leaves united by the theme of Russian poet Aleksandr Blok, 20 leaves devoted to the theme of the "Berlin. Moskau. Wosnessenskij" exhibition, 4 leaves devoted to "Triumf" Foundation 10th anniversary, with a folder, a printed copy of a cover of Voznesenskii's book "Aksioma samoiska", and a dust jacket of Voznesenskii's book "Stradivari sostradan'ia" designed by Voznesenskii.
      Aleksandr Blok.; "Triumf" Foundation.
    - Printed visual poetry1998; n.d., Printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon / on photopaper, 13 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten additions, some are slightly damaged. (Othertype 25, Folder 1)
      13 leaves of printed visual poetry, including "krugomety".
    - Visual poetry1995; n.d., Marker / pen / pencil on paper; printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon / on photopaper, 17 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten additions, some are damaged. (Othertype 25, Folder 2)
      17 leaves of visual poetry, including "krugomety".
      Leonardo da Vinci.
    - Printed visual poetry1998; n.d., Printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon, 14 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten additions, some are damaged. (Othertype 25, Folder 3)
      14 leaves of printed visual poetry, including "krugomety".
    - Printed visual poetryn.d., Printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon / on photopaper, 9 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten additions, some are slightly damaged. (Othertype 25, Folder 4)
      9 leaves of printed visual poetry, including "krugomety".
      Salvador Dali; Anise Koltz.
    - Printed visual poetryn.d., Printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon / on photopaper, 10 leaves of different size total, some with short handwritten additions, some are slightly damaged. (Othertype 25, Folder 5)
      10 leaves of printed visual poetry, including "krugomety".
    - Visual poetry1998 [?]; n.d., Printed visual poetry on paper / on paper attached to cartoon; marker on paper with numerous handwritten additions and / or poetic texts, 13 leaves of different size total, some are slightly damaged. (Othertype 25, Folder 6)
      13 leaves of visual poetry, including "krugomety". On the other side of a piece of cartoon there is an announcement (attached) about a photoexhibition to be opened on February 5, 1998 in Voronezh (does not seem to have any connection with the content of the folder).